# **RESUME**



# Educator/Linguist

Personal Info

Name: Siti Syamimi binti Saad

Address: No 15, Lorong Salam, Titi Gajah 06550 Alor Setar, Kedah.

DOB: 20 December 1994 H/P Number: 012-4533638 Email: syamimisd@gmail.com

Summary

Dedicated, creative and resourceful graduate majored in teaching English and has a deep interest and passion in the field of linguistics and translation. Possess a skill in handling various computer software and positive working attitude with the willingness to learn and obtain new experience for self-improvement.

### Education

7013 - 7017 BACHEIOLOLEUM(AHOH HESOLUTION)	2013	- 2017	Bachelor of Education (TESOL) (Hor	121
--	------	--------	------------------------------------	-----

Universiti Sains Malaysia, Pulau Pinang

CGPA: 3.52

Major: TESOL (Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages)

Minor: Interactive Multimedia

2012 - 2013 Matriculation

Kolej Matrikulasi Kedah

CGPA: 3.54

2010 - 2011 SPM

SMK Tunku Abdul Malik, Alor Setar, Kedah

Result: 7A 3B

# Work Experience

Sept 2017 - Nov 2017 Substitute Teacher

SMK Seri Gunong, Alor Setar Kedah

Job Description:

- 1. Facilitate the students to complete their exercise.
- 2. Complete organisational work such as writing report and build a lesson plan.
- 3. Administered and corrected tests and quizzes in a timely manner.

Feb 2017 - June 2017 Practical Teacher

### SMK Khir Johari, Sungai Petani Kedah

Job Descriptions:

- 1. Develop interesting course plans to meet academic, intellectual and social needs for students.
- 2. Implement after school tutoring hours with other hours to help students in need of extra attention.
- 3. Administered and corrected tests and guizzes in a timely manner

### July 2016 - August 2016 Practical Teacher

SMK Batu 17, Guar Chempedak Kedah

Job Description:

- 1. Assist language teachers in the classroom.
- 2. Facilitate the students to complete their exercise.
- 3. Complete organisational work such as writing report and build a lesson plan.

### Skills

### Computer Skill

- Microsoft Words
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Microsoft Excel
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After Effect
- Adobe Flash
- Adobe Premiere Pro

### Language Skill

- Malay Language (Advanced)
- English Language (Advanced)
- Mandarin (Basic)

# Extracurricular Experience

International Leadership and English Language Camp (LELAC) 2014/2015

(Facilitator)

Creative Writing Workshop

(Participant)

Hockey Festival (2013)

(Facilitator)

Community Service Program (BSMMUSM)

(Facilitator)

- Coordinate effective language activities to ensure the understanding, interest and cooperation of students.
- Help to facilitate various students in conducting activities.
- Enhance creative and academic writing skills.
- Engage critically with creative texts across multiple genres.
- Provide medical aids for the participants in need.
- Provide needed assistance to community agencies and to the people served by the agencies.
- Help to give out basic necessity to the homeless in Georgetown, Penang.

# Reference

Mr. Sandra Gesan A/L Balakrishnan (Mentor Teacher)

SMK Khir Johari Jalan Pangkalan,

Sungai Petani,

08000 Sungai Petani

Kedah

Puan Maznah binti Ali (Practical Supervisor)

Universiti Sains Malaysia

11800 USM

Pulau Pinang